Prime!
擎天柱！
Special agent Fowler, to what do we owe...
福勒探员 有何贵…
What else, Cons!
还能干什么？霸天虎呗！
I chased them off from some hard ordinates.
我把他们赶至绝路
But not before they blew me out of sky.
他们也把我敲了下来！
Hm£¬again?
又输了？
They tried to smash and grab for the dingus.
他们想抢我的“那玩意儿”
The... what's it?
哪个玩意儿？
Dynamic Nuclear Generation System.
动态核能发电系统（D.N.G.S）
A.K.A. dingus.
也就是“那玩意儿”
It's a prototype energy source. I'm porting to the coast for testing.
是种供能原型机 我正要送到西岸去测试
That's absurd.
太荒唐了
Why would Starscream bother with such primitive technology?
红蜘蛛怎么会看上这种原始技术？
I'm guessing they are making a big bad primitive weapon, of mass destruction.
我猜他们是想制造一种大规模杀伤性武器
If this baby would melt down,
如果这个小东西被熔毁
it would radiate this state and the four next door.
这里和周边四个州都可能受到辐射污染
I¡¯m a sittin' duck here, Prime.
我现在束手无策 擎天柱
I need you to spin up your bridge,
我要你们打开环陆桥
and send the dingus to its destination before the Cons come back for it.
在虎子们杀回来之前 火速把“那玩意儿”送到目的地
I'm afraid that sending such a volatile device through the Ground Bridge is out of the question.
用环陆桥传送这种极不稳定的装置 恐怕不妥
If there were to be an accident during transmission,
如果在传送途中发生意外
the radiation of which you speak could propagate through Ground Bridge vortex,
辐射产生的污染就会通过环陆桥的漩涡扩散
and harm all 50 states, and beyond.
会波及50个州 甚至更远
You got any better ideas?
你还有别的高招吗？
Ahh... No need, Agent Fowler.
啊…不必了 福勒探员
I will handle the driving.
我来负责开车
It's gonna be a long trip.
这一路可够我受的
Autobots, roll out.
汽车人 出发！
We are locked on your coordinates, Optimus.
你们的坐标已经锁定 擎天柱
Barring any complication you should reach the drop off point by sun down.
不出意外的话 你们会在日落前到达目的地
Move it, gramps!
快走啊 死老头！
Agent Fowler, is that really necessary?
福勒探员 有这个必要吗？
Uh, don't tell me one of those textbook drivers.
别跟我说你是个“三好司机”
They are transporting in an un-armed civilian truck.
货物由一辆无武装的民用卡车运送
Send in the ground units.
派地面部队出击
You know, you're saving my bacon here, Prime.
知道吗 这次你帮了我的大忙 擎天柱
I am proud to be of service.
能帮上忙 我很荣幸
Of course, not like I'd need your help if you and the Cons had stuck to turning up your own corner of Galaxy.
当然 要是你们和虎子在自己的地盘上打 我就更轻松了
Are you suggesting that no evil existed in your world before we arrived?
你的意思是 在我们到来之前 你们的世界是太平盛世吗？
Well, it was a¡­ different evil.
这个嘛 这是…两码回事
How about some radio?
听听收音机怎么样？
You seem like a Nashville sound kind of guy.
你这种人大概喜欢听乡村音乐
That's the one,
就是他
the Con who shot me down.
是那个虎子把我打下来的
Who is he? Wingnut? Dingbag? Skyguy?
他叫什么？翼形螺母？二愣子？还是鸟人？
Watch your rear views.
看看身后
Feel like a little constricted without the use of my fist here, boss.
施展不开拳脚 真是浑身发痒啊 老大
Remain in vehicular mode unless absolutely necessary.
不到万不得已 必须保持车辆形态
A whole team of Cons!
居然来了一群虎子
What? I'm not picking up anything.
什么？我没发现任何信号
They must be utilizing a cloaking technology.
他们一定使用了屏蔽技术
Pull over.
停车！
Well I'll be dipped.
哎呀 我好怕怕啊！
Our assailants are not Decepticons, they are humen.
袭击我们的不是霸天虎 是人类
Humen?
人类？
Oh, please. Taking on our Bots?
拜托 敢挑衅汽车人？
They are road kill!
他们死定了！
Gentlemen,
先生们
stop their engines.
让他们停车
Who are these guys?
他们是哪路的？
Autobots, maintain your cover,
汽车人 保持伪装形态
and apply minimal force, disarmament only.
使用最小武力 解除武装即可
Those are not civilian drivers.
那些司机不一般
Could use some air.
来点新鲜空气吧
Prime, bear right!
擎天柱 右转！
Care to tell me everything I want to know?
我问什么 你就答什么！
I do hope you take better care of that dingus than you do your captives.
希望你处理“那玩意儿”时 别这么笨手笨脚
Special Agent William Fowler here.
我是特工威廉・福勒
Identify yourself!
报上名来！
I am Silas,
我叫塞拉斯
by of greater consequence to you,
不过你可能更熟悉另一个名字
we are MECH.
我们是“机械党”
Fair warning,
给你个警告
we will be helping ourselves to your device,
我们自有办法拿到你的仪器
even if it means inflicting cacualties.
不惜任何伤亡代价
Is that so?
真的吗？
Tell me, Sygh?
告诉我 小塞
What's the market price for a dingus these days?
“那玩意儿”现在的市价是多少？
What makes you think we intend to sell it, Agent Fowler?
你觉得我们是想卖掉它吗 福勒特工？
There is a war brewing,
战争正在酝酿
between the new world order and the newest.
世界秩序即将焕然一新
And the victor, will be the side armed with the most innovative technology.
胜者 必定是拥有最尖端科技的一方
So Sigh,
我说小塞
you think MECH has all the most radical tech?
你觉得“机械党”已经掌握了最尖端技术吗？
Definitely not civilian drivers.
司机绝不是一般人
Later, Sigh.
回头见 小塞
Agent Fowler, do not take your Silas lightly.
福勒探员 不要小看这个“塞拉斯”
Megatron preached the very same ideology
威震天当时宣扬的正是这种理念
before plunging Cybertron into the Great War that destroyed our world.
后来塞博特恩爆发了大战 我们的星球毁于一旦
Optimus, prepare to initiate phase 2.
擎天柱 准备实行第二步计划
5 miles ahead to the south,  you will reach the rendezvous point.
向南五英里处 就是会合地点
"5 miles ahead to the south,  you will reach the rendezvous point."
“向南五英里处 就是会合地点”
So, the Autobots are outside the confines of their base,
这么说 汽车人已经离开了他们的基地
and sound otherwise engaged.
似乎正忙得焦头烂额
Which means, they will never see us coming.
也就是说 他们对我们毫无防备
Find them, and scrap them!
找到并消灭他们！
Yes, lord Starscream.
遵命 红蜘蛛陛下！
There's our destination point.
那儿就是目的地
Autobots, keep a tight formation.
汽车人 保持紧密队形
Tactical lair,
战术失误
only one way out.
只有一个出口
Air support?
空中支援？
Ours or theirs?
是敌还是友？
Optimus, you have company.
擎天柱 有麻烦了！
Military fired on one of their own?
军方怎么向自己人开火？
Sir, the dingus.
长官 “那玩意儿”！
The dingus didn't melt down.
“那玩意儿”没有熔毁
No, it did not.
是的 确实没有
Agent Fowler, I'm afraid that if you and we are to survive.
福勒探员 为了你和汽车人的安全
It has become absolutely necessary to drop our cover.
恐怕我们现在不得不解除伪装了
So the rumors are true.
原来那些传言是真的
Living technology stands before us,
机械生命体就站在我们眼前
though perhaps not for very long.
但恐怕他们长久不了
Remain here.
作壁上观吧
Will do.
悉听尊便
After a long road trip,
跑了这么远
it feels good to get out of the car,
终于可以变形了
stretch my legs,
活动活动筋骨
and kick some tailpipe.
踢爆它几个排气管！
Sir, if the dingus wasn't in the truck..
长官 如果“那玩意儿”不在卡车上…
Yes, that.
对 这个嘛
Special Agent Fowler, you need a jung life walking among titans?
福勒特工 和巨人一起共事 千万要小心
Come on, down. I'll introduce you.
下来吧 我给你们引见引见
In good time.
另择吉日吧
But in the moment I'm too busy wandering how the dingus might have vanished into thin air without a trace.
现在我很想知道 “那玩意儿”是如何凭空消失的
Now if you could excuse me,
失陪了
I have a train to catch.
我要去赶火车
Prime!
擎天柱！
Silas got wise to phase two!
塞拉斯识破第二步计划了！
I understand!
我知道了！
Prime! Do you read me?
擎天柱 能听到吗？
Prime!
擎天柱！
Optimus is down!
擎天柱受了重伤！
And MECH's gonna grab the dingus.
“机械党”要去抢“那玩意儿”了！
We need to think of something quick!
快想想办法！
You mean like a phase three?
你是说 来个“第三步计划”？
OK.
好吧
Come on, think!
开动脑筋！
Alright, if MECH wants the dingus,
好吧 如果“机械党”想得到“那玩意儿”
they have to get on that train.
他们必须上火车
What if we get on board first!
要是我们先上车呢
You know, run some human on human interference£¿
想想看 来个真人对打！
Absolutely not!
绝对不行！
Yea, that would be suicide.
没错 那等于自杀
Hello?! The United States of Meltdown?
拜托 想变成“大熔炉合众国”吗？
Lives are at stake?
人命关天啊！
Yes, yours!
是你们的命！
You want me to not only bridge you into a confined space,
你们要传送的地方 不光是密闭空间
but one traveling at 90 miles per hour?
而且移动速度每小时140多公里！
I can't even count the number of ways that can go wrong!
我根本无法想象可能出现的意外
Mass displacement trauma, twisted limbs, metal burn?
大面积错位损伤 四肢骨折 金属烧伤
Well, maybe not the last one.
呃 也许没有最后那种
Regardless,
不管怎么说
it is nearly impossible to fix Ground Bridge coordinates on something moving at that speed.
要把环陆桥坐标锁定在高速移动的物体上 几乎不可能
Would it help if we had access to the train's coordinates?
要是能…跟踪火车的坐标呢？
Well...
那另当…
Demobilize them.
解除他们的武装
We are in.
我们进来了
I read you, Jack.
收到 杰克
The cell phone com-link patch works.
手机通讯补丁很管用
Raf, MECH's landing on top of the train.
拉夫 “机械党”的人要在车顶降落
In about 20 seconds, you are gonna come to a fork.
大概20秒后 会有个岔口
Brace yourselves.
抓紧了
What happened?
怎么回事？
Hacker.
有黑客
Former hacker.
初级黑客
What?
什么？
And what have I been saying all alone about our technology?
我就说我们这技术不靠谱吧？
So what that buy us? 10 seconds?
这算什么？帮我们争取10秒钟吗？
Raf is using his touch.
拉夫失算了
You want a slice of this?
想吃我一斧子吗？
Well do you?
快来啊！
What she said!
我也一样！
Sir.
长官！
Retreat.
撤退
First rule of the combat,
作战原则第一条
never leave the enemy with the spoils.
绝不给敌人留下战利品
Ratchet, MECH's moved the train tracks.
救护车 “机械党”炸断了铁轨！
You need to bridge us out of here.
快把我们传送回去！
The soldiers, too.
还有那些士兵！
We've lost access to the train data.
我们无法跟踪火车的坐标数据！
I can't bridge you back without your coordinates.
没有坐标 我就没法接你们回来！
Optimus, Jack and Miko are on that train and MECH has blown the tracks!
擎天柱 “机械党”炸了铁轨 杰克和神子还在火车上
I'm on my way.
我正赶过去
Maximum overdrive!
全速前进！
Maybe we should jump?
我们跳车怎么样？
At 90 miles per hour?
时速可是140公里啊！
It's the impact or the meltdown, take you pick.
要么摔死 要么烧死 你选吧
What we were thinking volunteering for this?
我们当初干嘛非来不可？
Next time your need to do a better job of talking us of the situations.
下次你最好先想办法来脱险
Next time?
还有下次吗…
Or we can ourselves another few seconds if we are in the back of the train, right?
如果我们跑到车尾 是不是能多活几秒钟？
Miko, at least, we are in this together.
神子 至少 我们能死在一起
Raf, this is important!
拉夫 重要提示！
Make sure Bulkhead gets my guitar.
一定要把我的吉他留给隔板
Don't read the will just yet.
先别急着说遗言
Where is Optimus?
擎天柱在哪儿？
He has a train to catch.
他要赶火车
Well played, visitor.
身手不错嘛 天外来客
But MECH still has un-fielded advantages
但我们“机械党”不会善罢甘休
and we will find a way to level that playing field.
我们会有办法和你们对抗的
Even if we have to open you up.
就算要给你开膛破肚
To see what makes you tick.
也要摸清你们的老底
Optimus, are you and the children
擎天柱 你和孩子们…
intact?
都好吗？
Intact, Ratchet.
安然无恙 救护车
Crisis averted.
危机解除了
But the world in which we live is a different one than previously imagined.
不过我们脚下这颗星球 与想象中相去甚远
One which is bond its own Decepticons,
这里也有本土的霸天虎…
in human skin.
披着人皮的老虎